CHAN Sze Tung

CONTACT

- +852 9070 0487
- E nicolechan1217st@gmail.com
- A Broadview Court, No.11 Shum Wan Road, Wong Chuk Hang, Hong Kong

SKILLS

Communication Skills

Microsoft Office

SQL

Java

HTML & CSS

Javascript

LANGUAGES

Cantonese
English
Mandarin

CERTIFICATE

Experience Design (Foundation) Part-Time, H academy

- Build prototypes
- Developed comprehensive thinking
- Design and implementation
- Group project and presentations

PROFILE

Nicole is a passionate, friendly, and energetic student at the Baptist University of Hong Kong. She has gained people-facing experience from voluntary work and part-time jobs in swim coaching and tutorial lessons for children. Able to effectively self-manage during independent projects and collaborate as part of a productive team. Committed to utilizing my skills to further the mission of a company.

EXPERIENCE

Part-time tutor at Ensure Education

February 2022 - Present

- Handling the education centre's daily affairs
- Guiding students to solve their problems
- Proofreading students' homework, and teaching students new topics.

Part-time Swimming Coach at Island Sports

June 2021 - August 2022

- Teaching children to swim.
- Designing mini-games to engage children.
- Communicating with parents about their children's progress

EDUCATION

Hong Kong Baptist University Sep 2020 - Present

Bachelor in Computer Science,
Concentrated in Information System Analysis

Sacred Heart Canossian College Sep 2013 - June 2020

Secondary School

Electives include: BAFS (management), Physics, Biology

EXTRA-CURRICULAR ACTIVITIES

Treasurer at House in Secondary School

- · Financial planning and budgeting
- Financial reporting
- · Book-keeping